### Contact

+380676873447 (Mobile) valentin.sheboldaev@gmail.c om

www.linkedin.com/in/w-e-ll (LinkedIn) w-e-ll.com (Personal)

### Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)
PostgreSQL
MongoDB

## Languages

Russian (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)

# Valentin Sheboldaev

Currently looking for a job - Python Software Engineer

# Summary

NOW.

PR.sape

I'm a Python Engineer with a knowledge in Object Oriented Design and Programming. I'm passionate about building Python applications.

Python Development
3+ year knowledge in object-oriented python application development:  - Python, PostgreSQL, MongoDB/MongoEngine, AsyncIO, Threading/Multiprocessing  - Bottle/Aiohttp, Lxml, Re, Collections, Pillow, Selenium, Scrapy, PyTest, Mypy, Logger, Git, Docker, Jira, Linux  - Understanding of the Agile software development practices. Scrum and Kanban.  - Took part in team activities such as plannings, stand-up meetings,
code reviews, live demos.
FAMILIAR WITH:
- Celery, Redis, RabbitMQ, Apache Airflow, Pandas
LEARNING:
- Python Networking Programming
IN PAST:
SEO. Digital Marketing. Web Development
10+ years. Good expertise in search engine optimization (SEO). Google, Bing, Yandex - Setlinks, Gogetlinks, Blogun, Seopult, Megaindex, Mainlink,

- Sape, GetGoodlinks, Miralinks. Crowd marketing. Google PPC management services.
- content marketing: writing, rewriting, generation of unique content 7+ year experience in website development, wp-plugin development:
- fixed design, liquid or fluid design, responsive design
- CSS3, HTML5, Bootstrap, Wordpress, Joomla, (MySQL, PHP, JQuery novice)
- landing pages, portfolio, blogs, magazines, directory and contact pages, homepages

### **OBJECTIVE:**

-----

My objective is to obtain a Software Engineer position in a stable company with opportunities for growth.

# Experience

Smartwork Solutions GmbH Python Developer June 2019 - January 2020 (8 months) Kiev, Ukraine

- designed and developed new system components as a part of the backend team;
- custom user registration and management. Limit the number of active users in user management;
- developed image processor for concrete image converting strategy;
- bitmap and vector images import/export API, image conversion logic;
- developed and maintained existing backend components;
- added custom routines/jobs for content processing in tables and sections during word import;
- implemented database migrations with custom business logic on application startup;
- designed and implemented RESTful/Websockets APIs with Python 3.7 and MongoDB/Mongoengine.

HotelFriend AG
Python Developer
March 2018 - February 2019 (1 year)
Kiev, Ukraine

- developed applications to extract data from Booking, Hotels, Tripadvisor, HotelsCombined, Melia;
- created a robust, async, socks5 proxy, error-resistant crawler to scrape Google App;
- ran 32 parallel crawlers on 5 PC simultaneously, collected over half a million of hotels;
- scraped complete information about the hotel business profile;
- scraped Google Places using Google Place API;
- scraped search engine results for SEO tracking, collected domains for link builder;
- provided scraped data in formats like: json, csv, excel, xml, postgresql etc.

### **PNN Soft**

Python Developer

August 2017 - January 2018 (6 months)

Kiev, Ukraine

- designed and developed new system components, web-apps;
- developed and maintained existing back-end components;
- designed and implemented REST APIs with Python 3.5, Flask and MySQL;
- contact app, registration app, Google Places app, gallery app;
- updated customer web resources as needed;
- audit and optimization, competitor analysis, keyword research.

#### **BIOTECHNIK**

Web Developer

July 2016 - March 2017 (9 months)

Kiev, Ukraine

- designed and developed corporate website, wordpress theme development;
- back-end application development with complex product catalog;
- front-end (responsive design). HTML, CSS, Jquery, Bootstrap;
- custom wp-plugins development. design and develop new system components;
- ensured efficient and correct implementation of website;
- developed dynamic and interactive website that ensured high traffic, page views, and user experience.
- increased authority and trust-rating of website reputation management;

Advance Kazo Dental Clinic Python Developer. SEO January 2015 - March 2016 (1 year 3 months)

Kyiv, Kyiv City, Ukraine

- website development: front-end and back-end;
- audit and optimization, competitor analysis, keyword research;
- search engine optimization, link building;
- increased authority and trust-rating of website reputation management;
- maintained website and added more appealing features;

# Education

### **National Aviation University**

Specialist degree, Electrical engineering, electric power consumption systems. · (1999 - 2005)

### School of Internet Marketing EMPO

SEO Specialist, Search Engine Optimization · (2009 - 2010)

David Beazley - programmer, book author, trainer Python Programming Language LiveLessons

**Education Center "Specialist"** 

Object oriented python programming. Basics of SQL. PostgreSQL.

**Udemy Online Courses** 

REST APIs with Flask and Python